easyQue = [{ 'Question': 'A class cannot be declared:',  'Type': 'MCQ', 'Difficulty_Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'option1': 'Static',
            'option2': 'Private', 'option3': 'Default', 'option4': 'Object', 'Correct_Answer': 'Private'},
           {'Question': 'With inheritance, a derived subclass object can directly access any', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'With inheritance, a derived subclass object can directly access any',
            'Option2': 'Private superclass member', 'Option3': 'Public superclass member',
            'Option4': 'Protected, public or private superclass member', 'Correct_Answer': 'Public superclass member'},
           {'Question': 'What is the keyword used in java to create an object?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'This', 'Option2': 'New', 'Option3': 'Sync',
            'Option4': 'New()', 'Correct_Answer': 'New'},
           {'Question': 'An array holds:', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'Similar values of same data Type',
            'Option2': 'Different values of same data Type',
            'Option3': 'Same values of different data Types',
            'Option4': 'Different values of different data Types', 'Correct_Answer': 'Similar values of same data Type'},
           {'Question': 'Which of the following always need a Capital letter ?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'Class names and Strings', 'Option2': 'Objects and class names',
            'Option3': 'Fields and Strings', 'Option4': 'Data Types and fields', 'Correct_Answer': 'Class names and Strings'},
           {'Question': 'The default statement of a switch is always executed.', 'Type': 'T/F',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False',
            'Correct_Answer': 'False'},
           {'Question': 'Following code will result in: float num = 5/0;', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'Compilation error: Divisions must be in a try block',
            'Option2': 'Compilation error: DivideByZeroException', 'Option3': 'Runtime Exception',
            'Option4': 'No Error: a is NaN', 'Correct_Answer': 'Runtime Exception'},
           {'Question': 'Choose the appropriate data Type for this value: "1" ', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'String', 'Option2': 'Boolean', 'Option3': 'Int',
            'Option4': 'Char', 'Correct_Answer': 'String'},
           {'Question': 'Choose the appropriate data Type for this value: 1', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'String', 'Option2': 'Int', 'Option3': 'Double',
            'Option4': 'Boolean', 'Correct_Answer': 'Int'},
           {'Question': 'Which of the following is not a Java keyword?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'Main', 'Option2': 'Try', 'Option3': 'Integer',
            'Option4': 'String', 'Correct_Answer': 'Integer'},
           {'Question': 'Can you compare a boolean to an integer?', 'Type': 'T/F',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'False'},
           {'Question': 'What is the size of a Char in Java?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': '4 bits', 'Option2': '7 bits', 'Option3': '8 bits',
            'Option4': '16 bits', 'Correct_Answer': '16 bits'},
           {'Question': 'Primitive data Types are allocated on a stack', 'Type': 'T/F',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'True',
            'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'True'},
           {'Question': 'Choose the appropriate data Type for this field: kindOfBird', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'String', 'Option2': 'Int', 'Option3': 'Boolean',
            'Option4': 'Double', 'Correct_Answer': 'String'},
           {'Question': 'Following code will result in: int num = 6.7;', 'Type': 'MCQ',
            'Difficulty_Level': 'Easy', 'Option1': 'Compilation error', 'Option2': 'Runtime error',
            'Option3': 'Num being 6.7', 'Option4': 'Num being 6', 'Correct_Answer': 'Compilation error'}
           ]

mediumQue = [
    {'Question': 'A null reference may be used to access a static variable or method.', 'Type': 'T/F', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium',
     'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'False'},
    {'Question': 'If none of the private/protected/public is specified for a member, that member..', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'Is accessible publicly',
     'Option2': 'Is only accessible by other classes of the same package', 'Option3': 'Is only accessible from within the class',
     'Option4': 'Is accessible by the class and its subclasses', 'Correct_Answer': 'Is only accessible by other classes of the same package'},
    {'Question': 'Given the declaration : int [ ] ar = {1,2,3,4,5}; What is the value of ar[4]?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': '2', 'Option2': '3', 'Option3': '4', 'Option4': '5', 'Correct_Answer': '5'},
    {'Question': 'Which one needs a web page to run', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'Which one needs a web page to run', 'Option2': 'A Java Stand-Alone Application',
     'Option3': 'A Java Applet', 'Option4': 'A Java Class', 'Correct_Answer': 'A Java Applet'},
    {'Question': 'Which is not a part of defining an object?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'Description', 'Option2': 'Methods',
     'Option3': 'Associations with other objects', 'Option4': 'Name', 'Correct_Answer': 'Description'},
    {'Question': 'The methods wait(), notify() and notifyAll() in Object need to be called from synchronized pieces of code.', 'Type': 'T/F',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'True'},
    {'Question': 'An object could be ...', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'Anything', 'Option2': 'A data container', 'Option3': 'A program',
     'Option4': 'An Algorithm', 'Correct_Answer': 'Anything'},
    {'Question': 'Inner classes can be defined within methods.', 'Type': 'T/F',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'True'},
    {'Question': 'What is the main function of any variable?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'To add numbers together', 'Option2': 'To keep track of data in the memory of the computer',
     'Option3': 'To print words on the screen', 'Option4': 'To write Java codes', 'Correct_Answer': 'To keep track of data in the memory of the computer'},
    {'Question': 'Methods that are marked protected can be called in any subclass of that class.', 'Type': 'T/F',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'True'},
    {'Question': 'The last value in an array called ar can be found at index:', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': '0', 'Option2': '1', 'Option3': 'Ar.length',
     'Option4': 'Ar.length - 1', 'Correct_Answer': 'Ar.length - 1'},
    {'Question': 'Choose the best definition of an object', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'A Thing', 'Option2': 'An instance of a class', 'Option3': 'Something you wear',
     'Option4': 'Variable', 'Correct_Answer': 'An instance of a class'},
    {'Question': 'An abstract class can have non-abstract methods.', 'Type': 'T/F',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'True'},
    {'Question': 'What is the difference between private and public functions?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'Public functions are free, you have to buy private ones',
     'Option2': 'Public functions are the only ones you can download',
     'Option3': 'Public functions can be used by anyone, private can only be used by other code in the class you are writing',
     'Option4': 'Public functions canâ€™t be used', 'Correct_Answer': 'Public functions can be used by anyone, private can only be used by other code in the class you are writing'},
    {'Question': 'What is an instanceof?', 'Type': 'MCQ', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Medium', 'Option1': 'A methods in object',
     'Option2': 'An operator and keyword', 'Option3': 'An operator only', 'Option4': 'A keyword only',
     'Correct_Answer': 'An operator and keyword'}
    ]


hardQue = [
    {'Question': 'Native methods can be "abstract"', 'Type': 'T/F', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard',
     'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'False'},
    {'Question': 'Which one could be used as the main container in a Java application?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'JApplet', 'Option2': 'JFrame', 'Option3': 'JPanel',
     'Option4': 'JButton', 'Correct_Answer': 'JFrame'},
    {'Question': 'How to define a JButton with the caption test?', 'Type': 'MCQ', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'JButton aButton("test");',
     'Option2': 'JButton aButton=new JButton("test");', 'Option3': 'JButton aButton=new JButton(test);', 'Option4': 'Button("test") aButton;',
     'Correct_Answer': 'JButton aButton=new JButton("test");'},
    {'Question': 'A UML association from class A to class B means', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'Class B inherits from Class A', 'Option2': 'Class B is defined within class A',
     'Option3': 'Class B has an attribute of Type A', 'Option4': 'Class A has an attribute of Type B', 'Correct_Answer': 'Class A has an attribute of Type B'},
    {'Question': 'Class B inherits from Class A, what cannot be said:', 'Type': 'MCQ', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard',
     'Option1': 'B is a sub-class of A', 'Option2': 'A is a super-class of B', 'Option3': 'B has access to private members of A',
     'Option4': 'B has access to protected members of A', 'Correct_Answer': 'B has access to private members of A'},
    {'Question': 'A class can be transient.', 'Type': 'T/F', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'False'},
    {'Question': 'What is an Applet?', 'Type': 'MCQ', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'AA Java program that does not run through a web browser',
     'Option2': 'A Java program that is run through a web browser', 'Option3': 'An object-oriented programming language',
     'Option4': 'An interactive website', 'Correct_Answer': 'A Java program that is run through a web browser'},
    {'Question': 'Java keywords are written in lowercase as well as uppercase.', 'Type': 'T/F',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'False'},
    {'Question': 'What does AWT stands for?', 'Type': 'MCQ', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'Advanced Window Toolkit',
     'Option2': 'Abstract window Toolkit', 'Option3': 'Adjust Window Toolkit', 'Option4': 'None of the choices',
     'Correct_Answer': 'Abstract window Toolkit'},
    {'Question': 'In an instance method or a constructor, "this" is a reference to the current object.', 'Type': 'T/F',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'True'},
    {'Question': ' _____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'JVM', 'Option2': 'JRE', 'Option3': 'JDK',
     'Option4': 'JDB', 'Correct_Answer': 'JDB'},
    {'Question': 'What is the return Type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'Object', 'Option2': 'Int', 'Option3': 'Long',
     'Option4': 'Void', 'Correct_Answer': 'Int'},
    {'Question': 'Garbage Collection is manual process.', 'Type': 'T/F',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'True', 'Option2': 'False', 'Correct_Answer': 'False'},
    {'Question': ' What do you mean by nameless objects?', 'Type': 'MCQ',
     'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard', 'Option1': 'An object created by using the new keyword.',
     'Option2': 'An object of a superclass created in the subclass.',
     'Option3': 'An object without having any name but having a reference.',
     'Option4': 'An object that has no reference.', 'Correct_Answer': 'An object that has no reference.'},
    {'Question': 'Which of the following is an immediate subclass of the Panel class?', 'Type': 'MCQ', 'Difficulty_Level': 'Hard',
     'Option1': 'Applet class', 'Option2': 'Window class', 'Option3': 'Frame class', 'Option4': 'Dialog class',
     'Correct_Answer': 'Applet class'}
    ]
